Guide to the Roy Rosenzweig papers, 1934-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: Labor History, 1960-1990s; (23 boxes)
  - Worcester Parks, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Worcester Parks, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Worcester Social Class, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Worcester Social Class, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Worcester Swedes, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Worcester Swedes, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Worcester Unemployment Notes, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Worcester: A Community Social Profile, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Worcester: Notes and Articles, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Worcester: Petitions, Saloon Keepers, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Worcester: Petitions, Saloon Keepers, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Work Relations in the Coal Industry: The Hand-Loading Era, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Work: Let There Be Song, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Workers and the American Economy: Data on the Labor Force, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Workers and Unemployment, 1970s-1980s (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Workers in American Fiction, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Workers of Worcester, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Working Blues: Labor and Leisure in Industrial America, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Working Class Historiography, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Working Class Worcester Ideas and Notes, 1970s (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - WPA Collection, 1990s (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - WPA Strike and Trials, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Written Labor Movement Pamphlet, 1954, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Series 3: The Park and the People, 1980s-1990s; (33 boxes)
  Research on New York City and Central Park generated in the 1980s and 1990s.
  - All Angels Church, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - American Heritage, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - American Heritage Long Version and To Do List, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - American Heritage Reviews, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - American Heritage: Database, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - American Heritage: Reader Survey Data, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - American Museum of Natural History Notes, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - American Science and Historic Preservation Society, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Bibliographical Information, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Bibliography: Central Park Research Notes, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Census Totals, 1855 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Central Park and New York Research, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Arrests, 1870-1890 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Biographies (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Conservancy, 1985-1990 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Central Park German Papers, 1850-1855 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Central Park German Papers, 1856-1863 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Central Park Irish Papers, 1884-1888 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1854 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1854 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1854 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1854 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1858-1864 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1858-1864 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Notes, 1858-1864 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1858-1864 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1865-1869 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1865-1869 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1870-1874 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1870-1874 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1870-1874 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Notes, 1875-1879 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1875-1879 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1875-1879 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1880-1884 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1880-1884 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1880-1884 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1885-1889 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1885-1889 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1885-1889 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1890-1891 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1890-1891 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1892-1894 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1892-1894 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Notes, 1892-1894 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Central Park Notes, 1895-1899 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1895-1899 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1900-1908 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1900-1908 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1900-1908 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1909-1911 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1909-1911 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1912-1916 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1912-1916 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1917-1922 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1917-1922 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1923-1926 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1923-1926 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1923-1926 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1923-1926 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1927-1929 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1927-1929 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1927-1929 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Notes, 1930-1932 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1930-1932 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1930-1932 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1933-1934 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1933-1934 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1933-1934 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1935 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Notes, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1941-1954 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1941-1954 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1941-1954 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1941-1954 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1950s (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Notes, 1955-1970 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1955-1970 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes, 1955-1970 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes, 1955-1970 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, 1970-1979 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Notes, 1970-1979 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Notes, 1980-1989 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Notes, 1980-1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Central Park Notes, 1980-1989 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Notes and News clippings, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Notes and News clippings, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Central Park Notes, misc., 1980s-1990s (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Preservation, 1980s-1990s (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Zoo, 1980s-1990s (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Zoo, 1980s-1990s (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Central Park: The Heart of the City, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Central Park: The Heart of the City, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 1-4, 1990s (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 1-4, 1990s (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 5-9 Notes and Revisions, 1990s (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 5-9 Notes and Revisions, 1990s (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 5-9 Notes, Ideas and Memos, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 5-9, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 9, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 9-10, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 11-12, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 12, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 12, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 13, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 14, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 14, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 14, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 14 Park Archives, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 14-15, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 14-15, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 15 Preservationist Bios, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - City of Boston Parks, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Co-author Comments: The Park and the People, 1990s (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Collaboration and Comments on Chapters, 1990s (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Comments and Feedback: The Park and the People, 1990s (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Commission Minutes to Discuss with Blackmar, 1990s (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Condemnation Records, 1980s-1990s (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Condemnation Records, 1980s-1990s (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Crime, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Crime, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Databases, 1990s (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopedia of American Biography, 1980s (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Franklin Park Coalition Bulletin, 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - General Research:NYC, 1980s-1990s (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - General Research:NYC, 1980s-1990s (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - General Research:NYC, 1980s-1990s (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - General Research:NYC, 1980s-1990s (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - General Research:NYC, 1980s-1990s (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - General Research:NYC, 1980s-1990s (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Graphics for The Park and the People, Chapters 1-6, 1990s (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Graphics for The Park and the People, Chapters 1-6, 1990s (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Graphics for The Park and the People, Chapters 1-6, 1990s (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Greensward Foundation, 1980s-1990s (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Interviews: Parks, 1980s-1990s (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Intro, Epilogue, Outline, 1990s (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Land, 1990s (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Land, 1990s (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Land and Surroundings, 1990s (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Land and Surroundings, 1990s (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Letters: James Beekman, 1980s-1990s (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Letters: James Beekman, 1980s-1990s (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Maps and Minutes, 1980s-1990s (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Marc Papers, 1990s (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Mayor's Papers and MSS Index, 1980s-1990s (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous New York Notes and Research, 1990s (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous New York Notes and Research, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Moses Papers: Robert Moses, Parks Commissioner, 1980s (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Museum Book, 1980s (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Museum Royalties, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Museums around Central Park, 1980s-1990s (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - National History Reports, 1980s (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - New York and Central Park: References, General, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - New York and Central Park: References, General, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - New York Historical Society, 1980s-1990s (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - New York Historical Society, 1980s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Olmsted and Park Theory, 1980s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Olmsted Association Papers, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Olmsted Notes, 1980s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Olmsted Papers, 1980s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Olmsted Papers, 1980s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Olmsted Papers, 1980s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Olmsted Papers, 1980s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Olmsted Parks Conference, 1980s-1990s (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets and Olmsted Parks, 1980s-1990s (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlets and Olmsted Parks, 1980s-1990s (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Park Commissioner Minutes, 1970s-1990s (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Park Commissioner Minutes, 1970s-1990s (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Park Commissioner Minutes, 1970s-1990s (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Park Commissioner Minutes, 1970s-1990s (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Park Commissioners, 1990s (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Park Commissioners, 1990s (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Park Department Papers, 1950s-1980s (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Park Department Records, 1900-1934 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Park Department Records, 1900-1934 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Park Reports, 1898-1931 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Park Reports, 1898-1931 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Park Reports, 1898-1931 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Park Reports, 1930s (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Park Reports and Minutes, 1980s (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Park Reports and Minutes, 1980s (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Park Reports and Minutes, 1980s (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Parks Budgets, 1878-1900 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Parks Conservancy Reports, 1982-1984 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Parks Council Papers, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Parks in the News, 1980s-1990s (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Parks Notecards, 1980s-1990s (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Payroll and Costs, 1960s-1970s (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and Costs, 1960s-1970s (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Penn Paper, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Petitions, 1980s (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Race Track Notes, 1980s-1990s (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - References: Newspapers, 1980s-1990s (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - References: Newspapers, 1980s-1990s (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Sage Papers: Parks, Olmsted, and Russell Sage, 1980s (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Seneca Village, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Seneca Village Exhibit, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Sex and Gender, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Squatters in Central Park, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Squatters in Central Park, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Supplements New York, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - The Park and the People, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - The Park and The People Publicity, 1990s (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - The Wealthy Citizens of New York, 1980s (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Theater and Amusements Notecards, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - To-Do: Museums, Parks, Grants, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - To-Do: Central Park, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Twentieth Century: General Articles, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Twentieth Century: General Articles, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Vaux Papers, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Welling Papers, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Xeroxes: Central Park, 1930s-1960s (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Xeroxes: Central Park, 1960s-1980s (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Xeroxes: Central Park, 1980s (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Series 4: The Presence of the Past, 1990-1999; (11 boxes)
  This series contains research related to the book The Presence of the Past.
  - AA 3.1-3.4, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - AA 3.13-3.16, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - AA 3.5-3.12, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - AA Frequency, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - AA Regression, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - African American, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - African American and Caucasian, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - African American Case Notes, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - African American Case Notes, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - African American Supplement, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - African American Survey Material, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - AI 5.1-5.4, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - AI Frequency, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Analysis of Variance, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Case ID, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Case ID (misc.), 1990s (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Case ID 1000+, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Case ID 1000+, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Case ID 1000-2000, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Case ID 1000-2000, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Case ID 1034h, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Case ID 2000-3000, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Case ID 2000-3000, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Case ID 2000-3000, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Case ID 3000-5999, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Case ID 3000-5999, 1990s (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Case ID 3000+, 1990s (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Case ID 3000+, 1990s (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Case ID 4000+, 1990s (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Case Notes 2000-3000, 1990s (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Case Notes 2000-3000, 1990s (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Caucasian, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Caucasian Case Notes, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Caucasian Case Notes, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Caucasian Supplement, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 5 Comments, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 5 Revisions, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Cross Tabs Activ 2, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Data, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Data, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Drafts, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Final Performance Report, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - General Notes, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - General Notes, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - How Americans Understand and Use the Past, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Logical Regressions Memo, 1994-1997 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - MA-4.1-4.4, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - MA 4.5-4.12, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Methodology and Survey Results, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Methodology and Survey Results, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Mexican American, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Mexican American Case Notes, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Mexican American Case Notes, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Mexican American Multiple Regressions, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Mexican American Multiple Regressions, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Mexican American Supplement, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Mexican American Survey Material, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Mexican American Test, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Mexican American Test, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Mexican and Caucasian, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Minnesota Indians, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Minnesota Indians, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Minority, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - MM Frequency, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Multiple Regression, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Multiple Regression, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - National Sample, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - National Sample, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - National Sample Supplement, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - NEH Grant, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Notes on Sample for Activ 2, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - NS 2.1-2.4, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - NS 2.6-2.16, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - NS Frequency, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Pine Ridge Case Notes, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Pine Ridge Case Notes, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Pine Ridge Case Studies, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Pine Ridge Case Studies, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Pine Ridge Supplement, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Pine Ridge Text, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Pine Ridge Text, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Pine Ridge Text, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Pre-Test Data, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Prospectus, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Regressions, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Regressions, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Regressions, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Reviews, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - South Dakota, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - South Dakota and Caucasian, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - South Dakota Indians, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - South Dakota Indians, 1990s (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - South Dakota Indians, 1990s (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - South Dakota Indians, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Survey Data for Presence of the Past, 1990s (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Text by Variable Activity Set, 1990s (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Text by Variable Activity Set, 1990s (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Text by Variable AH5-End, 1990s (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Text by Variable AH5-End, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Text by Variable AH5-End, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - The Presence of the Past, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - The Presence of the Past Notes, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - The Presence of the Past Notes, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - The Presence of the Past Notes, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Thelen, David, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Trustworthiness and Connectedness of Museums, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Trustworthiness and Connectedness of Museums, 1990s (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Trustworthiness and Connectedness of Museums, 1990s (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - US Residents as Demographic Variable, 1990s (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Visions of the Past (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Series 5: Oral History, 1970-2007; (7 boxes)
  Series 5 contains pamphlets, research, papers, notes and publications about oral history, specifically interviews and local VA history. This series also contains many how-to guides and information about classes regarding oral history.
  - A Do it Yourself Oral History Primer, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - A Note on the Duplication in the Life History Series, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - American International College Oral History Center, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - American Memory Fellows Program, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - American Memory Fellows Program, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Anderson, Everett (Life Histories), 1939 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Ascher, Sidney (Interviews), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Baltimore People, Baltimore Places, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Bess, Leila (Life Histories), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Black Settlement in Fairfax County, 1938-1939 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Byrd, Frank (Life Histories), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - City of Fairfax Historic Sites, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Deed of Gift to the Oral History Program, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Ellison, Walden and Weinstock (Life Histories), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Equipment for Oral History, 1980s (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Family History, 1980s (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Federal Theater Festival George Mason University, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Federal Theater Project and New Deal Culture of George Mason University, 1980s (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Final Report on the Oral History of the WPA Arts Project, 1983-1987 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Finding Our Past: A Guidebook for Group Projects, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Fitzpatrick, A. (Interviews), 1938 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Friedlander, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - FWP Manuscripts, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - George Mason Oral History Memos, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - GMU Oral History Notes, 1980s (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Growing Up On Lewis Street in the 1920's, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Guide to the Oral History of the American Left, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - How To Do Oral History, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - How To Tape, undated (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Journal of American History, 1990s (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Life Histories Project Guide to Authors, undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Life History Interviews by Earl Bowman, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Life History Interviews by Earl Bowman, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Local History How-To and Blank Questionnaires, 1970s (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Louise Archer School News clippings, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Maryland Manual of Oral History, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - National Archives FWP, 1980s (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - National Archives FWP Summary of Findings, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - New Deal Art: The Oklahoma Experience, 1933-1943 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - New Federal One, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Northern Virginia Bibliography Project, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Northern Virginia Oral History Collection: Interview Index, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Northern Virginia Oral History Project, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Northern Virginia Oral History Project Instructions and Sample, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Oral and Local History Pamphlets, 1980's (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Oral History, 1980-1990 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Oral History, 1990's (Box 80, Folder 1)